OK, so now in this clip we're going to talk about idling.
I go back to your pole, your friend, whatever is going to hold you up while you're trying to do this.
As we said before, you're going to start with the unicycle in front of you and the pedal, at a kind of forty-five degree angle, rock up on to it, holding on.
I'm putting all my weight on to this pedal.
Find that other pedal.
Now, when you have all the weight on this foot, what you're going to do is just start rocking back and forth with your other foot.
So, I'm leaning all my weight here, and I'm just pushing forward and backward with this foot. And, I don't really; I have the pedals coming up, probably around a forty-five degree angle.
I don't really have them, I don't, when I'm rocking on the idle, I'm having it from here to here, pretty much.
I'm not coming up too high, when I'm idling.
You don't really have to do that.
It just keeps you, it keeps you up straight, you can't just, and you can't just stay on your unicycle stationary.
You have to be rocking back and forth to stay up.
So, that's the reason you idle.
And this is after you practice idling for awhile, holding onto something and then just keep all your weight on this foot, and just let go, and see how many you can do.